Student Activities Office: Subject Folders UA292 UA292
University of Rochester
- Fraternities: Theta Chi, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Includes a pledge final and a residence contract.
- Fraternities: Theta Delta Chi, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Includes information on the fraternity's history for pledges and a letter to pledges' parents.
- Fraternity House Closing Forms, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Contains rules for houses during the summer and other vacations and a vacation report form.
- Fraternity Social Program Form, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  Contains a Weekly Social Program Report form.
- Fraternity Summer Reports, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  Contains filled-in summer report forms.
- Friends of CORE, 1958-1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Includes several event posters and material for the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP).
  CORE stands for Congress on Racial Equality.
- Frosh Directories, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Contains correspondence about sending copies of the University's directory to other colleges and a letter about adding a "Hints to Parents" section to the directory.
- Frosh Summer Orientation, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Contains a letter of welcome and schedule of events for parents.
- Frosh Week, 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Frosh Week, 1961-1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Includes a manual for student activities groups for the 1967/1968 academic year.
- Frosh Week, 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Includes statistics about incoming classes, evaluations of freshman week activities by committee members, a questionnaire for freshmen for use in academic advising, and a course information booklet.
- Frosh Week, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Includes a brief analysis of the incoming class in the Admissions Office newsletter.
- Frosh Week 1960s, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Includes material on freshmen convocation.
- Frosh Week 1960: Registration and Reception (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Frosh Week 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Frosh Week 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Contains information on registration and reception for women students.
- Frosh Week 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Contains committee reports.
- Frosh Week 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Contains a 1962 Student Directory and committee reports.
- Frosh Week 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Includes a foreign student orientation schedule.
- Frosh Week 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Frosh Week 1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Contains letters to incoming freshmen.
- Frosh Week 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Frosh Week 1963: Evaluations (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Contains evaluation reports from faculty and staff members.
- Frosh Week 1963: Men (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Includes a report on activities and a pamphlet on academic honesty.
- Frosh Week 1963: Women, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Contains filled-out evaluations.
- Frosh Week 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Frosh Week 1964, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Includes a list of 1962 committee members and a corrected schedule for 1964.
- Frosh Week 1964 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  Includes a copy of the Association of Women Students Handbook for 1964/1965.
- Frosh Week 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Includes an activities bulletin for the week of October 6 (which was not Frosh Week) and a poster to upperclassmen asking that they stop taking freshmen's beanies so the freshmen can be properly hazed by having to wear them.
- Frosh Week 1964: Committee Budgets (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Frosh Week 1964: Convocation, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Contains convocation programs and reports from 1963 and 1964.
- Frosh Week 1964: Social Committee (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Includes a contract for the musical group The Rivermen.
- Frosh Week 1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Frosh Week 1965 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Frosh Week 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Includes invitations to banquets, a brochure about the events of the week, and a commencement program.
- Frosh Week 1965: Directory (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Frosh Week 1965: Printing (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Contains material sent out May 10, 1965 to incoming freshmen and a letter about the summer orientation program.
- Frosh Week 1965: Social Committee (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Frosh Week 1965: Special Arrangements (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Frosh Week 1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Includes the 1966 freshman handbook and freshman week program.
- Frosh Week 1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Includes freshman week material for incoming students, such as city brochures. Also includes material for upperclassmen involved in freshmen week
- Frosh Week 1966, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Includes directions to Frosh Camp and correspondence about traffic incidents in 1965 related to Frosh Week.
- Frosh Week 1966, 1960,1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Includes a copy of the magazine Orientation, a copy of the 1966 Frosh Week program, a copy of the 1966 Parents' Weekend program, and a brochure from 1960 about the rising cost of college tuition.
- Frosh Week 1966 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Includes filled-in party approval forms.
  The Party Approval Committee considered applications for parties on campus.
- Frosh Week 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Frosh Week 1966: Co-Chairmen Material, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Frosh Week 1966: Committee Co-Chairmen Material (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Frosh Week 1966: Executive Council Material (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Frosh Week 1966: Extracurricular Activities, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Frosh Week 1966: Mailings (Box 10, Folder 18)
  Includes mailings for freshmen and for committee members, and also includes a copy of a Orientation magazine.
- Frosh Week 1966: Nametag (Box 25)
- Frosh Week 1966: Social (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Includes contracts for musicians and nametags for chaperones.
- Frosh Week 1966: Special Arrangements (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Frosh Week 1966: Special Arrangements Report (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Contains a report about the Special Arrangements Committee's activities.
- Frosh Week 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Frosh Week: Decorations, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Contains a notebook from the University book store used by Barb Goldberg. It contains handwritten notes, documents and ephemera stapled and taped into the pages.
- Frosh Week: Men, 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Includes information on planning the faculty-student softball game.
- Glee Clubs, 1958-1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Contains material for the men's and women's glee clubs. Includes performance programs, a brochure on the women's club, and an itinerary and information booklet for a trip to Canada the men's group took.
- Graduate Living Center, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Contains the student manual and constitution of the residence hall government.
- Gridiron, 1949-1959 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  This was the football magazine and program for games published through the Board of Control.
- Ham Radio, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Contains an advertisement for free radiograms (telegrams sent by Ham radio).
- Handbook, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Contains the 1964/1965 handbook for undergraduate students, 1965/1966 Association of Women Students handbook, and a report on the 1965/1966 undergraduate handbook by the editors.
- Hellenic Council, 1956-1962 (Box 11, Folder 12-14)
- Hotels and Travel, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Includes local hotel and motel information for visitors and information about a tour of Europe for students.
- Hourly Payroll Form, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Identification Cards, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  Contains planning information about the implementation of identification cards for students. Includes several sample cards and advertisements from card companies.
- India Association, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Contains a Republic Day celebration program and planning material.
- Indicator, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  This was a magazine published by the University about engineering.
- Integration, 1952-1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Contains documents pertaining to the merger of the women's and men's colleges on the River Campus, completed in 1955.
- Intercollegiate Association of Women Students, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
  Includes program booklets, reports on the regional convention, and advertisements for the 1966 regional convention.
  The regional convention was held every two years and in 1964 was held at the University.
- Intercollegiate Association of Women Students, 1961-1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Includes promotional material for the University and Monroe County, a banquet program, several newspaper articles about the University, and a poster for the 1964 regional convention.
- Intercollegiate Association of Women Students, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Includes an agenda for the 1958 IAWS regional convention, a program for an IAWS luncheon at the State University of New York at Oswego, and material for various other conventions.
- Intercollegiate Association of Women Students: National, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Contains the 1965 IAWS Booklet and a 1964 letter about a model college orientation program.
- Intercollegiate Association of Women Students: Regional Conventions, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
  Includes material from the 1964 Rochester regional convention, the 1964 fall sub-regional convention at Syracuse University, 1962 Penn State Convention, and receipts of purchases from the Rochester chapter.
- Intercollegiate Association of Women Students: Regional Conventions: Nametag, 1964-1966 (Box 25)
- Interfraternity Council, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Interfraternity Council: Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Interfraternity Council: Fraternity Retreat, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Includes 7 photographs of a fraternity display at an activity fair and reports including more photographs and press clippings.
- Interfraternity Council: Housing Committee Expansion, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Contains material about the desire for new fraternity houses on campus for the fraternities without them.
- Interfraternity Council: Judicial, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Includes a letter to fraternities about responsibility for enforcing social rules.
- Interfraternity Council: Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Interfraternity Council: National Interfraternity Council Correspondence and Publications, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Includes copies of Interfraternity Views and News, a 1963 National Interfraternity Conference Program and Report booklet, a 1963 National Interfraternity Conference Public Relations pamphlet, and the 1964 National Interfraternity Conference Yearbook.
- Interfraternity Council: Newsletters, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Interfraternity Council: Public Relations, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Contains an editorial from the Democrat and Chronicle about actions taken by the Interfraternity Council to decrease hazing, a student activities and events information sheet, and a booklet titled Your Book of Ideas for a Constructive Public Relations Program.
- Interfraternity Council: Rules, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Contains a draft of the summer rules for fraternity houses.
- International Club, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Includes a poster for an Afro-American Folkloric Troupe performance, a poster for the lecture "An American View of U.S. Foreign Policy in Africa," and an events schedule.
- Interpres, 1948-1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Includes a memo about the Todd Union yearbook collection, tips for salesmen, and results of a 1949 survey conducted by UCLA of various colleges' yearbooks.
- Interpres: Editor's Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Intersorority Council, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Contains the constitution of the Intersorority Council.
- Intersorority Council, 1956-1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Includes a report on sorority participation from 1962.
- Jesters, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Includes advertisements for the show UP, tryout posters, a script for The Night after Tonight by Edward Mendelson, and playbills for Straw Hat, The Ten Dollar Bill, and Knit Me a Plaid Jeep.
- Jesters: Budget, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Contains the 1967/1968 budget.
- Keidaeans, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Includes certificates of initiation.
  At the time this organization was the senior men's honors society.
  Materials concerning Keidaeans' initiation ceremony have been moved to the Keidaeans collection.
- Key Issue Forms, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Mail, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  Includes time sheets for employees of the mail room.
- Marsiens, 1953-1966 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Includes information on fundraisers, a history of the society, and surveys (with their results) and reports that were given to faculty and students.
  This organization was the senior women's honor society.
- Meditation Room, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Mendicants, 1956-1963 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  This organization was the junior men's honor society.
- Men's Dining Center, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Contains a document titled "Guide for Scheduling and Supervision of Third Floor, Men's Dining Center."
- Men's Residence Open House History, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Includes a letter to staff advisors about rioting, lists of resident advisors, and a report on open house policy history at the University.
  Open houses were times when residence halls would allow students of the opposite sex to be in the halls and socialize with the residents.
- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  Includes a holiday meal schedule.
- Modern Dance Club, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Contains a letter about the organization's budget.
- Music: General, 1955-1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Includes a Strong Auditorium Concert Series schedule, Eastman School performance schedules, Glee Club programs, Baroque Ensemble programs, chamber concert programs, Mozart Weekend schedules and program, practice room sign-in sheets, a spring 1964 tour itinerary, a Protestant Chapel program, a Stravinsky Weekend program, schedules of concerts, a syllabus for Music Appreciation 1-2 in 1956, and press clippings and a newsletter about the Eastman Philharmonia's trip to Europe.
- New Groups, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Contains the rules of procedure for writing group constitutions.
- Ninth Masque Players, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Contains two articles about upcoming performances and the origin of the group.
  A summer theater group.
- Nite of Sin, 1960-1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Includes musician contracts and reports about the success of the event that also describe its history.
  A party held by the junior class the night before the junior prom.
- Office Supply Information, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Organizational Membership Notices, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Outing Club, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Includes information about the 1967 intercession ski trip, ski team information, a Genesee Valley Hiking Club schedule from 1965, and posters for interest meetings for skiing, "Bike Hikes," and camping trips.
- Outing Club, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Outing Club: Bicycle Trips, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Includes a poster and material for a trip to Cedar Springs Park.
- Outing Club: Cabin, 1926, 1932-1935, 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Includes a copy of Wesleyan College's Campus Chest newspaper with a 1932 article about its outing club's cabin use, material about the purchase of a cabin, material about Oberlin College and its cabin use, and photographs of a cabin from the 1930s.
- Outing Club: Constitution, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Outing Club: Forms, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Outing Club: Horseback Riding, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Outing Club: Membership, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Includes a letter about a gathering of Central New York outing clubs and joint trips for the clubs.
- Outing Club: Others, 1950-1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Contains newsletters for other colleges' outing clubs.
- Outing Club: Skiing, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
  Material for the intercession trips of January 1959, 1960, 1961, and 1962 (the last canceled due to poor skiing conditions).
- Outing Club: Trip to Letchworth Park, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Includes several maps of the park.
- Outside Group Activities, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Includes a room reservation packet and a concert program for the Men's Glee Club trip to Canada in 1963.
- Parents Guidebook, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Includes a guidebook from 1960 and an edited book from 1962 for a future year, possibly 1963 or 1964.
- Parents Letters, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Contains 2 letters: one about increasing tuition and the other a notification about a Parents Advisory Council meeting.
- Parents Weekend, 1961-1967 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Includes programs for folk singing concerts and for moving up day during Parents Weekend.
- Parents Weekend 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Includes invitations to banquets. Also includes material for both the 1962 and the 1963 Parents Weekends.
- Parents Weekend 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Includes 1967 programs and schedule, and a Parents Weekend folder that was specially decorated for the event.
- Parents Weekend: Business Manager, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Parents Weekend: Student Activities Office, 1963-1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Includes an undated program, possibly from 1966.
- Party Application, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Party Approval Committee, 1954-1966 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  Includes the University's policies on alcohol use.
- Party Approval Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Party Approval Request Forms, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  Includes party posters.
- Party Approvals, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  Includes party application forms, Todd Union Committee activity reports, and a Student Activities Office 1964/1965 calendar.
- Party Manual, 1962-1966 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Includes the manual, directions for the proper cleaning of Todd Union, and the Snack Bar floor plan.
  The manual was published by the Student Activities Office.
- Phi Beta Kappa, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Contains lists of initiates.
- Photographic Club, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Contains material related to the school's darkroom: planning, design, budget, keys, and schedule.
- Placement Office, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Includes job opportunity notices in summer bulletins and reports about post-graduation employment of University of Rochester students.
- Pre-Medical Society, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Contains the society's constitution and a draft constitution.
- Printing, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Includes a poster for Shakespeare's Twelfth Night and a brochure on a lecture series titled "Competition or Conflict in International Business."
- Prologue, 1952-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Includes posters advertising the literary magazine and notices about workshop meetings.
- Pumpkin Society and Other Ideas to Think About, 1955-1966 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Contains an invitation to an event and minutes from the event, planning documents and schedule for an end–of-exams party, a Theta Delta Chi End of Exams Beer Blast poster, and a plan for a smoker.
- Recommendation Letters, 1962-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Contains letters of recommendation and letters of congratulations for achievements.
- Red Cross, 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Includes conference schedules, material from the Red Cross Inter-College Council, and the 1961/1962 Annual Report for the Inter-College Council.
- Red Cross Yearbooks, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Contains Red Cross Inter-College Council yearbooks for 1962/1963 and 1963/1964.
- Religion, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Contains a copy of the the booklet Religion on Campus at the University of Rochester with a welcome letter and printed versions of the sermon series "Elegies in a University Churchyard."
- Religion Booklets, 1955-1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Includes copies of the booklet Religion on Campus at the University of Rochester, programs from religious services, and the senior convocation program from 1955.
- Religious Organizations, 1956-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Includes sermon booklets, bulletins, sermons 2-8 in the sermon series "Elegies in a University Churchyard," photographs of religious services, and posters for lectures, study groups, and dinners.
- Religious Survey, 1965/1966 (Box 17, Folder 3-6)
  Contains filled-out surveys and instructions. The survey is a general opinion survey to get an idea of what the typical college student thinks about various issues. In addition to asking students their religious affiliation, surveys asks questions about topics such as what their average day consists of, the roles of men and women in society and domestic life, and what they think a college education should consist of.
- Religious Survey, 1965/1966 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Residence Halls, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Includes projected numbers of residents, applications for off-campus housing, material for State University of New York at Brockport and Rochester Institute of Technology off-campus programs, and a brochure for a new Syracuse University residence hall.
- Residence Halls, 1959-1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Includes material from hall governments, material about the planning of the Hill Court residence halls as well as Phases II and III residence halls, material about residence advisors, and a "Best of Bogart" film series brochure.
- ROTC and NROTC, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Contains two press releases.
  ROTC stands for Reserve Officer Training Core and NROTC stands for Naval Reserve Officer Training Core.
- Rugby Club, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Contains a single membership list.
- Rules and Regulations, 1958-1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Includes an outline of material for speakers on "Radiation, Its Biological Effects, and the Fallout Problem."
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Includes a newspaper from Brandeis University called From the Lasker Fellows that has an article about Sane, correspondence with other schools about their chapters and pamphlets about organizations at other schools.
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Includes a brochure on anti-nuclear positions.
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Includes letters to government officials petitioning for more nuclear regulation.
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Includes event posters and many clippings from newspapers such as the New York Times and the Campus Times.
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy) Material, 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  Includes Student Peace Union bulletins from the University of Chicago. Also includes articles and brochures about nuclear policy from various sources including the United States government and United Nations.
  Sane was short for the organization Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy.
- Sane (Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy) Material, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Includes event posters, The Yardling publication from Harvard, and New York Times and Washington Post articles.
- SAVE, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Contains a thank you letter for electing members to the College Cabinet.
- Senior Bulletins, 1960-1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Includes Placement Office bulletins; progress reports for the classes of 1963, 1964, and 1966 (which were published in a class's sophomore year); and a post-graduation plan report for the class of 1963.
- Snack Bar, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Includes party reservation schedules for the snack bar.
- Social and Traditions Committee, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Contains a budget for the upcoming 1965/1966 year.
- Social Behavior Board, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)